open_question_bank_data = [{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Peter Molyneux was the founder of Bullfrog Productions.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science: Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The HTML5 standard was published in 2014.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Mythology","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Norse mythology, Thor once dressed as a woman.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Greenland is almost as big as Africa.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Coca-Cola&#039;s original colour was green.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The surface area of Russia is slightly larger than that of the dwarf planet Pluto.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Politics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The S in Harry S. Truman stands for &quot;Samuel&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the comic book &quot;Archie&quot;, Betty is friends with Veronica because she is rich.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Vehicles","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The Japanese Shinkansen beat the French TGV&#039;s speed record for fastest electric rail train.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"111,111,111 x 111,111,111 = 12,345,678,987,654,321","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The Southeast Asian island of Borneo is politically divided among 3 countries.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Studio Ghibli is a Japanese animation studio responsible for the films &quot;Wolf Children&quot; and &quot;The Boy and the Beast&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Sports","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Peyton Manning retired after winning Super Bowl XLIX.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Mythology","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"According to Norse mythology, Loki is a mother.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"United States President John F. Kennedy was assassinated during his presidential motorcade in Atlanta, Georgia on November 22nd, 1963.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Solid Snake is actually a clone from the DNA of Big Boss in the Metal Gear Solid series&#039; history.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the &quot;Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya&quot; series, the narrator goes by the nickname Kyon.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"United States President Ronald Reagan was the first president to appoint a woman to the Supreme Court. ","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Spadefish&quot; will attack you.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The French word for &quot;glass&quot; is &quot;glace&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The Lego Group was founded in 1932.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The song &quot;Mystery Train&quot; was released by artist &quot;Little Junior&#039;s Blue Flames&quot; in 1953.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the &quot;Toaru Kagaku no Railgun&quot; anime,  espers can only reach a maximum of level 6 in their abilities.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Mythology","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Greek mythology, Hera is the goddess of harvest.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The names of Roxas&#039;s Keyblades in Kingdom Hearts are &quot;Oathkeeper&quot; and &quot;Oblivion&quot;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Terraria, you can craft the Cell Phone pre-hardmode.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science: Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The first dual-core CPU was the Intel Pentium D.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The Hundred Years&#039; War was fought for more than a hundred years.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"A caterpillar has more muscles than humans do.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Board Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"&quot;PAYDAY: The Heist&quot; is a sequel to the board game &quot;Payday&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Sports","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In association football, or soccer, a corner kick is when the game restarts after someone scores a goal.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"All of these maps were in &quot;Tom Clancy&#039;s Rainbow Six Siege&quot; on its initial release: House, Clubhouse, Border, Consulate.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Norway has a larger land area than Sweden.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Politics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Nazi Germany surrendered on Harry Truman&#039;s birthday while he was president.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Television","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klingons respect William Shakespeare, they even suspect him having a Klingon lineage.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Stagecoach owned &quot;South West Trains&quot; before losing the rights to FirstGroup and MTR in March of 2017.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"L&#039;H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with indeterminations.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Actor Tommy Chong served prison time.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The character that would eventually become Dr. Eggman was considered for the role of Sega&#039;s new flagship mascot before Sonic was.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Tigers have one colour of skin despite the stripey fur.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The most frequent subconscious activity repeated by the human body is blinking.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The commercial UK channel ITV stands for &quot;International Television&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In &quot;Minecraft&quot;, gold tools are faster than diamond tools.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In the game &quot;Until Dawn&quot; Emily is the only playable character who can be killed by another playable character directly.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Codemasters is the developer of the Gran Turismo series.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In the Resident Evil series, Leon S. Kennedy is a member of STARS.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}]